



## **Facundo Erhardt**

Nationality: Argentinian Date of birth: 14/02/1992 Gender: Male

**Complex Service Serv** 

**Website:** <a href="https://facuerhardt.github.io/">https://facuerhardt.github.io/</a>

• Home: praça mouzinho de albuquerque 124 6°, 4050-115 Porto (Portugal)

#### **ABOUT ME**

I started my career as python developer and then moved to video games developer, where I learned how to use Unity3D engine, which is my current favorite tool. I love creating new worlds, characters and stories. I also like to explore new technologies in order to create better and more fun experiences for players.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Programador web Cogocode** [ 20/08/2022 - 20/12/2022 ]

**City:** Resistencia **Country:** Argentina

Frontend Development

- I develop the user interface.
- Web page development.

## Video games designer

**MD8 Games** [ 05/06/2021 - 15/08/2022 ]

**City:** Buenos Aires **Country:** Argentina

Video Game Development

- I create Characters 2D & 3D.
- Game Design.
- Level Design.
- I develop video game scripts.

## **Software developers**

**Freelancer** [ 18/02/2020 – Current ]

City: Buenos Aires Country: Argentina

**Backend Development** 

- I develop the user interface app.
- I create ux element interactions.
- I create scripts with OPP.
- I graph metrics of your business.

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

## Web Development & Data Science

Platzi Digital University [ 2020 - Current ]

## **Mobile App Development**

Madrid University - Google Activate [ 04/2020 - 06/2020 ]

## Videogame Development

National Technological University Buenos Aires [ 2019 - 2020 ]

#### **LANGUAGE SKILLS**

Mother tongue(s): **Spanish** 

## Other language(s):

## ingles

LISTENING A2 READING A2 WRITING B1

**SPOKEN PRODUCTION A1 SPOKEN INTERACTION A1** 

#### **DIGITAL SKILLS**

#### **Video Games**

Unity 3D / Game design / Renpy / C# / Visual Studio/ Visual Studio Code / Godot Game Engine

#### **Frontend**

JavaScript, HMTL5, CSS / Javascript React

#### **Backend**

Java / Python / Android Studio / Eclipse IDE

#### Design

Adobelllustrator / substance painter / Design tools (CANVA/Figma)

## Soft skills

Responsible, proactive, attention to detail / I am quick and curious in learning new software / team-work in team